

MICHAEL FUKUI

Web Developer

About Me

Utilizing over 10 years of hospitality industry experience and an Associate's Degree in Jazz Studies to develop web applications, applying interpersonal skills and user-focused design skills to create intuitive and engaging digital solutions.



916-996-0572



mr.fukui@yahoo.com



Sacramento, CA

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/michael-fukui

Portfolio:

https://github.com/mrfukui/portfoli o-website

Github:

https://github.com/mrfukui/portfoli o-website

Skills + Tools

- JavaScript/TypeScript
- Python
- React/React Native
- Angular
- Django
- CSS
- HTML5

Experience

Recipe Application: Python | Django | Heroku June 2024 | https://mrfukui.github.io/portfolio-website/recipe-app.html

- Developed a full-stack web application where users can login, add new recipes, search recipes according to ingredients, or view statistics based on recipes.
- Created and ran tests to ensure objectives were reached and designed a modern and responsive interface.

Movie Application: TypeScript | Angular | TypeDoc May 2024 | https://mrfukui.github.io/portfolio-website/fukuis-flixes.html

- Developed a front-end application using Angular to display movie information and create favorite movie lists.
- Created documentation using TypeDoc to explain functionality and technical aspects of the application.

Mobile Chat Application: JavaScript | React Native | Expo April 2024 | https://mrfukui.github.io/portfolio-website/chat-app.html

- Developed a mobile application where users can send and receive text, images, location, and audio.
- Application designed for Android and iOS devices and data could be stored and retrieved offline.

Education

Certificate in Full-Stack Web Development | CareerFoundry August 2023 - July 2024

 Project-based learning and experience using industry standard programming languages, libraries, and frameworks with one on one guidance from a tutor and mentor.

Associates in Arts in Jazz Studies | American River College August 2016 - May 2020

Employment

Server | Bj's Restaurants and Brewhouse 2021 - Present | Sacramento, CA

• Facilitated training for new staff, emphasizing clear communication and concise instruction to ensure smooth onboarding.

Bartender | Sauced BBQ and Spirits 2018 - 2020 | Sacramento, CA

• Utilized problem-solving skills to resolve customer issues promptly and maintain high satisfaction levels.